Are you suffering from the payoff
syndrome? It's when you make solid
investments into your game like lessons
and really hard practice and now you
expect all this work to pay off in your
next competitions. You see expectations
are a big source of evil for our mental
game because they create a lot of
pressure. Expectations are the unwritten
rules and standards and demands that a
player puts on him or herself. I should
win this match. I must reach the
quarterfinals. I cannot fail and lose to
this person. It's all fail or pass, good
or bad, do or die. It doesn't work like
that in competition. There are no
guarantees. There's you giving yourself
the best chance for success when you put
in all the hard work. Enjoy the process
and the progress and when it's time to
compete, put the hammer down without any
expectations. Go to work. Good luck.